kwa@cs.net

www.linkedin.com/in/kevinwaolden

I am a newly-trained full-stack web developer with years of experience in the software and consulting industry. I am customer focused and see technology as a means of helping people solve business problems by working on my own or as a member of a team to complete projects on time and on budget.

WEB DEVELOPMENT TOOLS

Front-End: HTML/CSS/SASS, JavaScript, jQuery, Angular, React

Back-End: Rails/ActiveRecord, Express Databases: PostgreSQL, MONGO, SQL

Sample Project: M*A*S*H Fansite: https://kevin-golden-mash-fansite.herokuapp.com/

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Notable Solutions, Inc. (Rockville, MD)

9/2011 - 10/2014 **Corporate Solutions Architect**

Supported inhouse sales staff and resellers with demonstrations, presentations, proofs of concepts, statements of work.

- Managed 100+ machine VMWare environment used for sales efforts, including managing SharePoint and other document management system servers
- Managed training program for junior sales reps
- President's Club, 2012

ZyLAB US (McLean, VA)

1/2007 - 9/2009

Technical Engineer

- Provided support for sales/installations of ZyIMAGE product line to customers and resellers
- Managed implementation of Zylmage product at US CBP
- Produced demonstrations, presentations, proposals, statements of work for installation and customization of ZyIMAGE product line

iLumin/CA (Herndon, VA)

9/2005 - 12/2006

Sr. QA Engineer

- Led SWAT team to complete testing and prepare Mailbox Manager product for shipment
- Created pre-sales questionnaire, reviewed/approved marketing materials and documentation
- Onsite and remote installations of Mailbox Manager, Compliance, and Discovery products
- Developed proofs of concept with partners and potential customers

CereSoft. Inc. (Silver Spring, MD)

1/2005 - 8/2005

Operations Manager

- Built/maintained ASP environment hardware, operating systems, and application software
- Build/maintained communications networks, including VPNs to connect customer and vendor sites, and FTP data transfer processes
- Supported customers during implementation of large project, including on-site user training and telephone/email support
- Wrote technical specifications, statements of work, performed installation for new customers

Technology Business Solutions (Mt. Laurel, NJ)

10/2003 - 12/2004

Field Service Technician

- Supported tenants in an office suite business
- Installed, managed, troubleshot desktops, printers, networks, VPN connections
- Periodic server maintenance and user training

eLink Communications (Bethesda, MD)

Technical Consultant

- Pre-sales support of connectivity products, including T1s, DS-3s, Verizon TLS circuits, technical services, and hardware/software sales
- Coordinated requirements definition, engineering, installation, and customer satisfaction for nonstandard products

CERTIFICATIONS

Microsoft Certified Professional (MCP)
Cisco Certified Network Administrator (CCNA)
CompTIA Security+

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

Benchmarks/Proofs of Concept Training Sales Personnel, Resellers, and Users

Demonstrations and Presentations Document Management

Cost Justifications Document Capture (Scan/Index/OCR)

Proposals/RFP Responses Project Management

Reseller Support Requirements/Statements of Work Competitive Analysis System Testing and Troubleshooting

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Web Development Intensive, General Assembly, Washington, DC MS, Technology Management, George Mason University, Fairfax, VA UNIX Certificate, George Washington University, Washington, DC BS, Political Science, Northern Illinois University, DeKalb, IL